Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Artifacts and Memorabilia Collection, 1888-2004 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Travel Items, undated, (1 Box)
  - Blue JWT South America ticket holder, undated (Box TR1)
  - Bottle sun tan coconut lotion by JWT Rio, undated (Box TR1)
  - Brown leather JWT luggage tag, undated (Box TR1)
  - JWT luggage tag, undated (Box TR1)
  - Navy leather JWT London map of London booklet, undated (Box TR1)
  - Packaged JWT map for Europe, undated (Box TR1)
  - Pair of wooden JWT Rio sandals, undated (Box TR1)
  - Picture of JWT Travel Bag, undated (Box TR1)
  - Souvenir bottle with sand design, JWT Brasil, undated (Box TR1)
  - White JWT Rio beach towel, undated (Box TR1)
- T-Shirts, 1980-1996 and undated, (5 Boxes)
  - Archives Weekend, Second Retired Directors, Duke University, 1990 (Box TS1)
  - Honourably Retired Directors Weekend, Duke University, 1990 (Box TS1)
  - Latin America Region Managers Meeting, Duke University, 1992 (Box TS1)
  - The Commodores Club, Stratford-Upon-Avon, England, 1992 (Box TS1)
  - 3rd Commodore's Club Reunion, Mas de Torrent, Spain, 1994 (Box TS2)
  - JWT Hong Kong polo, undated (Box TS2)
  - Mystic Commodore's Club, 1996 (Box TS2)
  - Old Owls Meeting, Duke University, 1995 (Box TS2)
  - I survived Typhoon Thompson, 1988 (Box TS3)
  - 125th Anniversary, made for Lisbon, 1989 (Box TS3)
  - Blue outline likeness of J. Walter Thompson, undated (Box TS3)
  - Hering World, in Portuguese, 1996 (Box TS3)
  - James Webb Young Workshop, Philippines, 1988 (Box TS3)
  - JWT Detroit Carnival, 1993 (Box TS3)
  - Red outline of Don Johnston with words I never give up, undated (Box TS3)
  - I'm just the type vanity tee, undated (Box TS4)
  - JWT Mexico 40th Anniversary, undated (Box TS4)
  - JWT Philippines commemorating JWT's help with the Revolution, 1986 (Box TS4)
  - JWT T-plan, undated (Box TS4)
  - JWT USA, undated (Box TS4)
  - NYA Scramble, undated (Box TS4)
  - Black Troutbeck, Second Commodore's Club Reunion, 1993 (Box TS5)
  - JWT Baby Shirts (Blue and Pink), undated (Box TS5)
  - JWT NY Walkathon, 1986 (Box TS5)
  - JWT Owl, undated (Box TS5)
  - Thompson Cup, 1980 (Box TS5)
- Young Tigers Program, 1994 and undated, (1 Box)
  - Hangzhou baseball cap, 1994 (Box YT1)
  - Hangzhou folder with program and notepad, 1994 (Box YT1)
  - Hangzhou tote bag, 1994 (Box YT1)
  - Ornate fans, undated (Box YT1)
  - Plush animal, undated (Box YT1)
  - Thailand button, undated (Box YT1)
  - Thailand certificate, undated (Box YT1)
  - Thailand folder with program and notepad, undated (Box YT1)
  - Thailand hat, undated (Box YT1)
  - Thailand name tag: Anupan, undated (Box YT1)
  - Thailand polo shirt, undated (Box YT1)
- Miscellaneous Items, undated, (7 Boxes)
  - Blue JWT flags with gold eagle embossing, undated (Box MS1)
  - Box of spark plugs from JWT London, undated (Box MS1)
  - Copper stamp plates, undated (Box MS1)
  - J. Walter Thompson's black umbrella with wooden stem and marble handle etched with owls, undated (Box MS2)
  - Tight cover with stars, undated (Box MS3)
  - Time capsule, undated (Box MS4)
  - Various citations, undated (Box MS5)
  - JWT Detroit We've Got the Best Grade Across the Board display, undated (Box MS6)
  - Printing Plate for Congoleum ad proofs, undated (Box MS7)
  - Massachusetts Mutual print advertisement, 1960 (Signed by Normal Rockwell) (Box MS7)
    [Restriction on Access: Item is closed. See use copy in JWT Domestic Advertisements, Massachusetts Mutual.]